Guide to the University of Chicago Office of the President, Beadle Administration Records 1916-1968
University of Chicago Library
- Series IB: General Files, I-Z
  - Student Recruitment and the Draft, Deans Committee on, 1967 (Box 321, Folder 6)
  - Student Residences and Facilities, Committee on (advisory), 1964-1967 (Box 321, Folder 7)
  - Student Residences and Facilities, Committee on (advisory), report, drafts, 1964-1965 (Box 321, Folder 8)
  - Student Residences and Facilities, Committee on (advisory), report, final and supplementary, 1964-1968 (Box 321, Folder 9-10)
  - Student study-in, Administration Building, 1966-1967 (Box 322, Folder 1-2)
  - Students for a Democratic Society, 1965-1968 (Box 322, Folder 3)
  - Students, letters to parents of, 1964 (Box 322, Folder 4)
  - Student's status, 1968 policy on release of information to outside agencies (including Selective Service), 1968 (Box 322, Folder 5)
  - Students, study-in, Students Against the Rank (SAR), outside comments and clippings, 1966-1967 (Box 322, Folder 6)
  - Study of the College and University Presidency, 1959-1961 (Box 322, Folder 7)
  - Su-, general, 1964-1968 (Box 322, Folder 8)
  - Summaries of Proposals Submitted to Government Agencies, volume V, 1966 (Box 322, Folder 9)
  - Summaries of Proposals Submitted to Government Agencies, volume V, 1966 (Box 323, Folder 1-2)
  - Summaries of Proposals Submitted to Government Agencies, volume VI, 1967 (Box 323, Folder 3-5)
  - Summer faculty colonies, 1963-1965 (Box 323, Folder 6)
  - Summer quarter, 1961-1968 (Box 323, Folder 7)
  - Summer quarter, 1961-1965 (Box 324, Folder 1-2)
  - Superconductivity in science and biotechnology, 1966 (Box 324, Folder 3)
  - Superior Student, Inter-University on the (ICSS), 1962-1964 (Box 324, Folder 4)
  - Superior Student, publications, 1952-1962 (Box 324, Folder 5)
  - Surgery, Department of, 1961-1968 (Box 324, Folder 6-10)
  - Swarthmore College, Pennsylvania, 1962-1966 (Box 324, Folder 11)
  - Sweden, 1961-1965 (Box 324, Folder 12-13)
  - Swift, Harold Higgins, eulogy by, for Claire Dux Swift von der Marwitzm 1961 (Box 324, Folder 14)
  - Swimming and swimming pools on campus, 1960-1968 (Box 324, Folder 15)
  - Syllabi, 1947-1964 (Box 324, Folder 16)
  - Syracuse University, 1963-1965 (Box 325, Folder 1)
  - Szilard, Leo, 1961-1967 (Box 325, Folder 2)
  - T-, general, 1967-1968 (Box 325, Folder 3)
  - Taft, Robert A., Institute of Government, 1960-1966 (Box 325, Folder 4)
  - Tavern Club, 1961-1967 (Box 325, Folder 5)
  - Tax Economics of Charitable Giving, booklet, Arthur Anderson and Co., 1964 (Box 325, Folder 6)
  - Taxes, 1956-1968 (Box 325, Folder 7-9)
  - Taxes, medical faculty, housing, 1967 (Box 325, Folder 10)
  - Taxes, proposed changes in federal tax laws affecting endowed institutions, 1960-1964 (Box 325, Folder 11)
  - Taxwise Giving, a publication, 1965 (Box 325, Folder 12)
  - Taylor, Lieberfeld and Heldman, 1959-1968 (Box 325, Folder 13)
  - Teacher Education, 1961-1967 (Box 326, Folder 1)
  - Telecommunications, Office of Telephone Service, facilities and space, 1962-1968 (Box 326, Folder 2)
  - Telephone Service, 1961-1968 (Box 326, Folder 3-4)
  - Television, Ford Foundation, submission to FCC on educational television, 1966-1967 (Box 326, Folder 5)
  - Temple University, 1968 (Box 326, Folder 6)
  - Temporal Bone Bank Center for Ear Research, 1962-1968 (Box 326, Folder 7)
  - Tennessee, University of, 1962-1964 (Box 326, Folder 8)
  - Tenure policies, 1961-1967 (Box 326, Folder 9)
  - Terman, Mandel, 1960-1962 (Box 326, Folder 10)
  - Texas, Texan, 1967 (Box 326, Folder 11)
  - Texas, University of, 1961-1968 (Box 326, Folder 12-14)
  - Th-, general, 1962-1963 (Box 326, Folder 15)
  - TWO (The Woodlawn Organization) and the University of Chicago, clippings pertaining to, 1968 (Box 327, Folder 1-2)
  - TWO (The Woodlawn Organization) and the University of Chicago, media, 1961-1966 (Box 327, Folder 3)
  - Theoretical Biology, Department of, Committee on Mathematical Biology, 1961-1968 (Box 327, Folder 4)
  - Theoretical Biology, Department of, Committee on Mathematical Biology, annual reports, 1961-1965 (Box 327, Folder 5)
  - Theoretical Biology, Department of, Committee on Mathematical Biology, chairmanship, 1963-1967 (Box 327, Folder 6)
  - Theoretical Biology, Department of, Committee on Mathematical Biology, history, 1946-1963 (Box 327, Folder 7)
  - Theoretical Biology, Department of, Committee on Mathematical Biology, outside comments on chairmanship and conditions, 1963-1965 (Box 327, Folder 8)
  - Time schedules, 1961-1967 (Box 328, Folder 1)
  - Tishman Realty and Construction Company, 1965-1967 (Box 328, Folder 2)
  - To-, general, 1965-1968 (Box 328, Folder 3)
  - Toronto, University of, 1962-1966 (Box 328, Folder 4)
  - Traffic in the university area, 1961-1968 (Box 328, Folder 5)
  - Transportation of staff and students, air travel, 1961-1966 (Box 328, Folder 6)
  - Transportation of staff and students, bus service, 1961-1968 (Box 328, Folder 7-9)
  - Transportation of staff and students, carpool project, 1964-1966 (Box 328, Folder 10)
  - Transportation of staff and students, livery service, 1965-1968 (Box 328, Folder 11)
  - Transportation of staff and students, university automobiles, 1961-1963 (Box 328, Folder 12)
  - Travel expense policies, practices and procedures, 1961-1967 (Box 329, Folder 1)
  - Treasurer, Office of, 1963-1968 (Box 329, Folder 2)
  - Treasurer, Office of, budget and finance, 1963 (Box 329, Folder 3)
  - Treasurer of the University, Lloyd Randol Steere, 1961 (Box 329, Folder 4)
  - Treasurer's Office, 1961 (Box 329, Folder 5)
  - Treasurer's reports, 1962-1967 (Box 329, Folder 6)
  - Trust Officer's day at the University of Chicago, invitations extended to Trust Officers of Chicago banks, 1962 (Box 329, Folder 7)
  - Tu-, general, 1964-1966 (Box 329, Folder 8)
  - Tuesday Club, the, 1962-1965 (Box 329, Folder 9)
  - Tuition deferment loans, 1961-1967 (Box 329, Folder 10-11)
  - Tuition deferment loans, statements, 1960-1967 (Box 329, Folder 12)
  - Tuition deferment and revisions, 1961 (Box 329, Folder 13)
  - Tuition, payments in advance, plan for, 1961-1963 (Box 329, Folder 14)
  - Tuition plan, 1961-1966 (Box 329, Folder 15)
  - Tuition remissions, Laboratory Schools, 1961-1967 (Box 329, Folder 16)
  - Tuition remission, Teachers and MATS program, 1961-1962 (Box 329, Folder 17)
  - Tulane University, 1961 (Box 329, Folder 18)
  - Turkel, Henry, 1962 (Box 330, Folder 1)
  - Turkey, visitors to the university from, Sunnay, Cevdet, President of the Republic, 1967 (Box 330, Folder 2)
  - Turner, Olive Grace, 1963 (Box 330, Folder 3)
  - Tuskegee Institute, Alabama, 1959-1968 (Box 330, Folder 4)
  - Typewriters, 1962 (Box 330, Folder 5)
  - U-, general, 1964-1966 (Box 330, Folder 6)
  - Uganda, visitors to the university from, 1964 (Box 330, Folder 7)
  - Unemployment compensation, 1952-1966 (Box 330, Folder 8)
  - Union League Club, 1957-1965 (Box 330, Folder 9)
  - Unions, 1961-1962 (Box 330, Folder 10)
  - Unions, American Federation of Labor, Congress of Industrial Organization, 1961-1968 (Box 330, Folder 11-13)
  - Unions at the University, American Federation of State, County and Municipal employees, 1961 (Box 331, Folder 1)
  - Unions at the University, American Federation of State, County and Municipal employees, contract negotiations, 1961-1966 (Box 331, Folder 2)
  - Unions at the University, American Federation of State, County and Municipal employees, grievance cases, 1961-1966 (Box 331, Folder 3)
  - Unitarians, 1961-1968 (Box 331, Folder 4)
  - United Charities of Chicago, 1962-1967 (Box 331, Folder 5)
  - United Nations, 1961-1968 (Box 331, Folder 6-7)
  - UNESCO (United Nations Education, Scientific and Cultural Organization), 1960-1968 (Box 331, Folder 8)
  - UNESCO (United Nations Education, Scientific and Cultural Organization), ninth national conference of United States Commission for, Chicago meetings, 1962-1964 (Box 331, Folder 9)
  - United States, 1961-1968 (Box 332, Folder 1-6)
  - United States, 200th anniversary of founding "think" session conference, 1965-1966 (Box 332, Folder 7)
  - United States Air Force, 1961-1965 (Box 332, Folder 8)
  - United States Air Force, air research and development command, 1964 (Box 332, Folder 9)
  - United States Army Reserve Centers, 405th and 486th strategic intelligence detachments, 1962-1965 (Box 332, Folder 10)
  - United States Atomic Energy Commission, 1962 (Box 332, Folder 11)
  - United States Atomic Energy Commission, 1963-1968 (Box 333, Folder 1-3)
  - United States, Attorney General, 1965-1967 (Box 333, Folder 4)
  - United States Central Intelligence Agency, university involvement, 1963-1967 (Box 333, Folder 5)
  - United States, Civil Service Commission, 1955-1967 (Box 333, Folder 6)
  - United States, Commission on Science and Technology, 1962-1967 (Box 333, Folder 7)
  - United States, Commission on Science and Technology, Bill S. 1136 for establishment of a, 1965-1966 (Box 333, Folder 8)
  - United States Congress, House Committee on Science and Astronautic, 1965-1966 (Box 333, Folder 9)
  - United States Congress, House, Illinois, first district, 1959-1967 (Box 333, Folder 10)
  - United States Congress, Senate Committee on Aeronautical and Space Sciences, 1963 (Box 333, Folder 11)
  - United States, Department of Agriculture, 1961-1964 (Box 333, Folder 12)
  - United States, Department of Commerce, 1965-1968 (Box 333, Folder 13)
  - United States, Department of Defense, 1961-1967 (Box 333, Folder 14)
  - United States, Department of Health, Education and Welfare, 1961-1962 (Box 333, Folder 15)
  - United States, Department of Health, Education and Welfare, 1961-1962-1968 (Box 334, Folder 1-5)
  - United States, Department of Health, Education and Welfare, Bureau of Drug Abuse Control, 1967 (Box 334, Folder 6)
  - United States, Department of Health, Education and Welfare, faculty and other professional staff, questionnaires, 1953-1966 (Box 334, Folder 7)
  - United States, Department of Health, Education and Welfare, "Higher Education Planning and Management Data" reports, 1951-1963 (Box 334, Folder 8-9)
  - United States, Department of Health, Education and Welfare, Housing For Senior Citizens, Curriculum Development Conference, March 1962 (Box 335, Folder 1)
  - United States, Department of Health, Education and Welfare, Medical Assistance Advisory Council, 1968 (Box 335, Folder 2)
  - United States, Department of Health, Education and Welfare, Office of Education, review of data acquisition program in area of physical facilities, 1967 (Box 335, Folder 3)
  - United States, Department of Health, Education and Welfare, Office of Education, study of inter-institutional graduate cooperation, 1966 (Box 335, Folder 4)
  - United States, Department of Health, Education and Welfare, study on graduate of predominantly negro colleges, class of 1964 (NORC), 1967 (Box 335, Folder 5)
  - United States, Department of Health, Education and Welfare, task force on education, 1966-1968 (Box 335, Folder 6)
  - United States, Department of Health, Education and Welfare, university medical administrative group, 1961-1962 (Box 335, Folder 7)
  - United States, Department of the Interior, 1963-1967 (Box 335, Folder 8)
  - United States, Department of Labor, 1961-1964 (Box 335, Folder 9)
  - United States, Department of State, 1961-1968 (Box 335, Folder 10-12)
  - United States, Department of State, Foreign Service, 1961-1966 (Box 335, Folder 13)
  - United States, Department of State, US-Japan Committee on Scientific Cooperation, 1961-1968 (Box 335, Folder 14)
  - United States, Department of State, University of Chicago faculty travel abroad, 1963 (Box 335, Folder 15)
  - United States, Economic Opportunity Act 1964 (Anti-Poverty program), 1964-1968 (Box 335, Folder 16)
  - United States, Federal Communications Commission, 1965-1968 (Box 335, Folder 17)
  - United States, Federal Trade Commission, 1967-1968 (Box 336, Folder 1)
  - United States, Fifth Army Headquarters, Chicago, 1956-1964 (Box 336, Folder 2)
  - United States, general, 1961-1963 (Box 336, Folder 3)
  - United States, government contracts, survey on administration of research grants by federal agencies (Bureau of the Budget), 1963-1966 (Box 336, Folder 4)
  - United States, House Committee on, Un-American Activities, 1965-1967 (Box 336, Folder 5)
  - United States, House of Representatives Sub-Committee on Public Health and Safety, questionnaire, 1963-1964 (Box 336, Folder 6)
  - United States, Industry-Government Special Travel Task Force, appointed by President Johnson, 1967 (Box 336, Folder 7)
  - United States, list of senators and representatives in Washington by university background, 1966-1967 (Box 336, Folder 8)
  - United States National Aeronautics and Space Administration, space month, university participation, 1963 (Box 336, Folder 9)
  - United States National Student Association, 1963 (Box 336, Folder 10)
  - United States Navy, 1961-1964 (Box 336, Folder 11)
  - United States Navy, Naval Medical Research Institute, proposed training or retraining center, 1964-1965 (Box 336, Folder 12)
  - United States Navy, Office of Naval Research, 1961-1967 (Box 336, Folder 13)
  - United States, Office of Science and Technology, 1963-1965 (Box 336, Folder 14)
  - United States Peace Corps, university participation, 1961-1963 (Box 336, Folder 15)
  - United States Peace Corps, university participation, 1964-1968 (Box 337, Folder 1)
  - United States Postal Service, 1962-1968 (Box 337, Folder 2)
  - United States President, Office of the, White House staff visits to the university, 1966-1967 (Box 337, Folder 3)
  - United States President, presidential prayer breakfast, 1964-1968 (Box 337, Folder 4)
  - United States, President's central group of expert in domestic affairs (E.F. Goldman recruited group for President), 1964-1965 (Box 337, Folder 5)
  - United States, President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, 1962-1968 (Box 337, Folder 6)
  - United States, President's Science Adviser and Advisory Committee, 1961-1963 (Box 337, Folder 7)
  - United States, Public Health Service, 1960-1966 (Box 337, Folder 8)
  - United States Selective Service System, 1966-1968 (Box 337, Folder 9)
  - United States, Small Business Administration, 1961-1967 (Box 337, Folder 10)
  - United States, Social Security System, 1964 (Box 337, Folder 11)
  - United States, Veterans Administration, Hospital, proposed, 1963-1966 (Box 337, Folder 12)
  - United States, Veterans Administration, Hospital, proposed, 1963-1968 (Box 338, Folder 1-2)
  - United Student Aid Funds Incorporated, 1961-1965 (Box 338, Folder 3)
  - Universities Associated for Research and Education in Pathology, University of Chicago membership, 1964-1965 (Box 338, Folder 4)
  - Universities and colleges, media, Harper's magazine series, 1958-1961 (Box 338, Folder 5)
  - Universities Research Association, Inc., AEC negotiations for site selection for 200 BEV Accelerator Laboratory, 1964-1967 (Box 338, Folder 6-7)
  - Universities Research Association, Inc., Board of Trustees, 1965-1967 (Box 338, Folder 8)
  - Universities Research Association, Inc., Council of Presidents, 1965-1968 (Box 339, Folder 1)
  - Universities Research Association, Inc., National Accelerator Laboratory (Weston) (200 BEV Accelerator), 1965-1968 (Box 339, Folder 2)
  - Universities Research Association, Inc., organization, by-laws and articles of incorporation, 1964-1968 (Box 339, Folder 3-4)
  - Universities for Space Research, proposed, 1967-1968 (Box 339, Folder 5)
  - University Architect, Office of, 1962-1968 (Box 339, Folder 6)
  - University awards and prizes, Allyn, Arthur C. and Horace C. Fitzpatrick leadership awards, proposed, 1961 (Box 339, Folder 7)
  - University awards and prizes, Rosenberger, Jesse, medal, recipients of, Claassen, Howard Hubert, 1963-1964 (Box 339, Folder 8)
  - University awards and prizes, Rosenberger, Jesse, medal, recipients of, Coggeshall, Lowell Thelwell, 1968 (Box 339, Folder 9)
  - University awards and prizes, Rosenberger, Jesse, medal, recipients of, de Hevesy, George Carl, 1960-1961 (Box 339, Folder 10)
  - University awards and prizes, Rosenberger, Jesse, medal, recipients of, Fishbein, Morris, 1968 (Box 339, Folder 11)
  - University awards and prizes, Rosenberger, Jesse, medal, recipients of, Lohr, Lenox Riley, 1962-1963 (Box 340, Folder 1)
  - University awards and prizes, Rosenberger, Jesse, medal, recipients of, Malm, John G., 1964 (Box 340, Folder 2)
  - University awards and prizes, Rosenberger, Jesse, medal, recipients of, Millis, John Schoff, 1968 (Box 340, Folder 3)
  - University awards and prizes, Rosenberger, Jesse, medal, recipients of, Russell, John McFarlane, 1968 (Box 340, Folder 4)
  - University awards and prizes, Rosenberger, Jesse, medal, recipients of, Selig, Henry H., 1964 (Box 340, Folder 5)
  - University awards and prizes, Rosenberger, Jesse, medal, recipients of, Shannon, James Augustus, 1968 (Box 340, Folder 6)
  - University awards and prizes, student, honors awards assemblies, 1961-1967 (Box 340, Folder 7)
  - University calendars, 1962-1966 (Box 340, Folder 8)
  - University of Chicago Foundation, proposed, 1962 (Box 340, Folder 9)
  - University of Chicago Round Table, 1961-1968 (Box 340, Folder 10-11)
  - University College, 1961-1962 (Box 340, Folder 12)
  - University College, American Federation of Labor, Congress of Industrial Organization, educational program for leaders of trade unions in Latin America, 1960-1962 (Box 341, Folder 1)
  - University College, Basic Problems Self Study Committee, 1959-1961 (Box 341, Folder 2)
  - University College, Committee on, 1961 (Box 341, Folder 3)
  - University College, downtown center, 1962-1968 (Box 341, Folder 4)
  - University College, extension division, downtown center, fine arts program, 1961-1965 (Box 341, Folder 5)
  - University College, extension on quadrangles, 1962-1967 (Box 341, Folder 6)
  - University College, general, 1961-1962 (Box 341, Folder 7)
  - University College, government programs, 1961-1962 (Box 341, Folder 8)
  - University College, history, 1928-1962 (Box 341, Folder 9)
  - University College, labor education program, 1961-1963 (Box 341, Folder 10)
  - University College, name, 1960-1961 (Box 342, Folder 1)
  - University College, outside comments on relocating, 1961-1962 (Box 342, Folder 2)
  - University College, program of executive development for federal administrators, 1961-1962 (Box 342, Folder 3)
  - University College on the quadrangles, Committee to select a coordinator or director, 1961-1962 (Box 342, Folder 4)
  - University College, questionnaire administered to downtown center students, 1961 (Box 342, Folder 5)
  - University College, reorganization, J.T. Wilson memo, comments on adult education at Chicago, 1959-1963 (Box 342, Folder 6-7)
  - University College, space, 1953-1961 (Box 342, Folder 8)
  - University College, Supervising Committee on Self Study, 1957-1961 (Box 342, Folder 9)
  - University Corporation for Atmospheric Research, 1961-1968 (Box 343, Folder 1)
  - University Council on Education for Public Responsibility, 1961-1967 (Box 343, Folder 2-3)
  - University extension, bulletins, 1964-1966 (Box 343, Folder 4)
  - University extension, college, "Adult Education at the University of Chicago," 1959-1963 (Box 343, Folder 5)
  - University extension and college, basic program of liberal education for adults, 1961-1963 (Box 343, Folder 6)
  - University extension, college, "Bright New City," lecture series, 1967-1968 (Box 343, Folder 7)
  - University extension, Co-operative Program of Continuing Faculty Education, 1968 (Box 343, Folder 8)
  - University extension division, symposium inaugurating 76th year, 1967 (Box 343, Folder 9)
  - University extension, "the Monday Lectures," 1965-1968 (Box 344, Folder 1)
  - University extension programs, 1961-1968 (Box 344, Folder 2-5)
  - University extension, space, 64 East Lake Street, 1961-1966 (Box 344, Folder 6)
  - University Health Service Committee on Student Health Service (Advisory), 1962-1967 (Box 344, Folder 7)
  - University Health Service, faculty and staff, 1964-1967 (Box 344, Folder 8)
  - University Health Service, student health service, 1961-1968 (Box 344, Folder 9)
  - University of Illinois at Chicago Circle, 1965-1968 (Box 345, Folder 1)
  - University loan and gift fund, 1927-1963 (Box 345, Folder 2-3)
  - University memberships, The Wayfarers Club, 1961-1967 (Box 345, Folder 4)
  - University publications, New University Thought, 1960-1963 (Box 345, Folder 5)
  - University Policy on Submitting Rank to Draft Boards, Committee on the (Student-Faculty), reports, 1966-1967 (Box 345, Folder 6)
  - University publications, Board of Membership, 1964-1968 (Box 345, Folder 7)
  - University publications, New Individualist Review, 1961-1967 (Box 345, Folder 8)
  - University Record, 1966-1968 (Box 345, Folder 9-10)
  - University Record, 1968 (Box 346, Folder 1)
  - University Research Association, committee on relationships between University of Chicago and National Accelerator Laboratory, 1967 (Box 346, Folder 2)
  - University Senate, 1961-1968 (Box 346, Folder 3-4)
  - University Theatre, general, 1960-1966 (Box 346, Folder 5-8)
  - University Theatre, The Misanthrope, 1965-1967 (Box 347, Folder 1)
  - University Theatre, The Misanthrope, budget and finance, 1965-1967 (Box 347, Folder 2-3)
  - University Theatre, The Misanthrope, general, 1965-1966 (Box 347, Folder 4)
  - University Theatre, The Misanthrope, letters and memos, 1963-1966 (Box 347, Folder 5)
  - University Theatre, The Misanthrope, publicity, news clippings, brochures, 1965-1966 (Box 347, Folder 6)
  - University in Under-Developed Area of World, proposed establishment, May 1961 (Box 348, Folder 1)
  - Urban Education, Committee on, 1965-1968 (Box 348, Folder 2)
  - Urban Education Developmental Project, Early Education Research Center, 1967-1968 (Box 348, Folder 3)
  - Urban Education Developmental Project, feasibility study, final report, creation of Woodlawn experimental district, 1968 (Box 348, Folder 4)
  - Urban Education Developmental Project, Woodlawn experimental district, 1965-1968 (Box 348, Folder 5-7)
  - Urban Education, evaluation of the Youth Manpower Project of the Woodlawn Organization, 1968 (Box 349, Folder 1)
  - Urban Education, general, 1963-1968 (Box 349, Folder 2)
  - Urban Education, Research and Development Center in, 1965 (Box 349, Folder 3)
  - Urban Education, Research and Development Center in, early discussions and planning, 1961-1966 (Box 349, Folder 4)
  - Urban Education, Research and Development Center in, proposal submitted to United States Office of Education, 1965-1966 (Box 349, Folder 5)
  - Urban Education, Research and Development Center in, proposal submitted to United States Office of Education, 1965-1966 (Box 350, Folder 1-2)
  - Urban Education, Robert D. Hess, proposals, 1966 (Box 350, Folder 3)
  - Urban Education, Woodlawn Community Board, 1966-1968 (Box 350, Folder 4)
  - Urban Education, Woodlawn Community Board, membership, 1966-1968 (Box 350, Folder 5)
  - Urban Education, Woodlawn district, clippings pertaining to, 1966-1968 (Box 350, Folder 6)
  - Urban renewal, 1953-1964 (Box 350, Folder 7-9)
  - Urban renewal, American College Public Relations Association Convention, 1961 (Box 350, Folder 10)
  - Urban renewal, campus security, 1961-1964 (Box 350, Folder 11)
  - Urban renewal, Chicago, 1959-1961 (Box 351, Folder 1)
  - Urban renewal, Chicago Osteopathic Hospital, 1961-1962 (Box 351, Folder 2)
  - Urban renewal, crime and police, 1959-1963 (Box 351, Folder 3-4)
  - Urban renewal, foundations and proposals, 1961 (Box 351, Folder 5)
  - Urban renewal, George Williams College, 1960-1962 (Box 351, Folder 6)
  - Urban renewal, Gordon R. Clapp, 1961 (Box 351, Folder 7)